Kthan Graham

9405 Laurel Ledge Dr, Riverview FL, 33569 ♦ 813-727-0464 KthanGraham@hotmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a background in Programming, HR system implementation and Project Management, I understand the importance of the Programming foundations, effective SQL setup and solid teamwork. Building on my experiences, I hope to contribute by utilizing my knowledge and exerting myself in the functions of Programming.

EDUCATION

University of South Florida, Tampa

Tampa, FL

Bachelor of Health Science, concentration in HR managment 3.0 GPA

Graduated 2018

<u>Relevant Coursework:</u> Public Speaking, Medical Terminology, Intro to Computers & Tech, General Psychology, Intro to Health Professions, Dev Psychology/Life Span

Extracurricular Activities: Hum Anat/Phys I, Hum Anat/Phys II, Intro to Sociology, General Chemistry I, General Physics I, General Chemistry II, Bio Science I.

Hillsborough Community College, Brandon

Tampa, FL

Associates of science, Associates in Programing 3.0

(2019-current)

<u>Relevant Coursework:</u> Programming Logic, Database Design, Computer Operating Systems, Intro to Networking, Java Programming, Programming in C#, Mgmt Info Sys.

Extracurricular Activities: None

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Oasis Paychex April 2019 – October 2019

PEO Specialist/HR consultant

Tampa, FL

- Prototyped the new payroll/HR backend
- Developed Excel charts to help provide better QA on payrolls.
- Handled 50+ Clients Payrolls and assisted in their Human resources.
- Collaborated with senior leadership to determine the best course of action and develop new training programs to increase retainment in the company.
- Generated and uploaded weekly Payroll and HR reports for all clients.
- Left to pursue education in programming.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Tillys

August 2014 – September 2016

Sales Associate/In Store Visual Merchandiser (ISVM)

Brandon, FL

- Leverage excellent communication and interpersonal skills to 50+ customers a day.
- Examined, evaluated, and analyzed floor plans to find the best fit for our customer interaction.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- *Training:* Completion of 91 education courses through Paychex, 4 years of communication technology courses, 89 college credits.
- Leadership/Organizations: Company commander JROTC, Team lead in documentary competition, ISVM at Tillys.
- Skills: SQL data management, IT problem solving, HTML background, work with HR databases, Payroll, Pseudo code syntax, Modular Programming.
- Activities: Balloon comity at Paychex, Building multiple apps, Film competitions, 3D printing, 360Food.